Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Item 3: Missabe Iron Ranger, Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Item 4: Missabe Iron Ranger, Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Item 5: Martin P. Catherwood Library, Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Item 6: Fortieth Anniversary of the Mesabi Iron Company 1919-1959 A Short History By Arnold Hoffman, Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
    By Arnold Hoffman. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: mestanews, Publication (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Item 2: mesta news, Publication (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Item 3: mesta news, Publication (Box 34, Folder 51)
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Focus On Facilities, Publication (Box 34, Folder 52)
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Item 2: Handbook for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 34, Folder 53)
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 34, Folder 54)
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
    March 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Right-To-Work and Union Membership, Publication (Box 34, Folder 56)
    April 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: better to serve you, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Item 2: Methods-Time Measurement Training Program, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
    November 30-December 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The M.E.C. Management Conference, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Item 4: Home Of The MEC Management Conference, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Item 5: Methods-Time Measurement Training Program, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
    June 1-June 19. Item is in English.
- Box: 34, folder: (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Surgical Operation And Hospital Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 58)
- Box: 35, folder: 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Highlights Metropolitan Pittsburgh Project, 1959, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Transit News, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Transit News, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Transit News, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: transit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 1960 annual report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Management Letter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: the Northern Light, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Management Letter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management-Union Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Wages, Publication (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of Progress 1965-1966, Publication (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Report of Progres 1965-1966, Publication (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Year Of The Beginning 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Police And The Negro Myth And Reality, Publication (Box 35, Folder 8)
    By Burton Lvy. August-September. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Civil Rights Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Civil Rights Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Civil Rights Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Career Development Programs, Publication (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Research Division Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Career Development Programs, Publication (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: State of Michigan Civil Service Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Rules of the Civil Service Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 11)
    December 14. Item is in English.
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: State of Michigan Department of Labor Its Member Agencies And Their Functions, Publication (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: State of Michigan Department of Labor Its member Agencies And Their Functions, Publication (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Labor Mediation Board General Rules And Regulations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Information For The New Employee, Publication (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Regulations of the Michigan Employment Security Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Employers' Handbook, Publication (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Regulations of the Department of Labor Michigan Employment Security Commission, Publication (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: personnel policy guide for supervisors, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: personnel policy guide for supervisors, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Your Job at MSU, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Your Job at MSU, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Classification And Compensation Plan For Employees Of Michigan State University, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Summary of Benefits, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Revised Summary Of Benefits For Full Time Operations, Clerical, And Technical Personnel, Publication (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor Mediation Board, Publication (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Working together at Michigan Plastic Products, Inc., Publication (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Bureau of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Institute Of Labor And Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Institute of Labor And Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Human Relations Program Of The Survey Research Center, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: A Method For Studying The Relationship Between Communication Structure And Attitudes In Complex Organizations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
    By Eugene Jacobson. February 4-5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: This Is Michigan State University 1969 Facts Book, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Publications of the Institute for Social Research, Publication (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Bureau Of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: 66/67 Annual Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Institute For Social Research, Publication (Box 35, Folder 21)
    September-December. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Institute For Social Research, Publication (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Institute for Social Research, Publication (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Part-Time Employment Service, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: a personnel program for the non-academic personnel of The University of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Instruction Manual Interim Grievance Procedure Non-Academic Personnel Univeristy Hospital The University Of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
    March 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: All Members Of Supervision, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Career Opportunities in Biological and Health Sciences Research, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Secretarial and Office Opportunities at The University of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: You And Your Job At The University Of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Policy Handbook For MSU faculty 1968, Publication (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Education Research Service, Publication (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: The University of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: The University of Michigan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Human Relations Program Of The Survey Research Center, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Second Annual Report of the Survey Research Center, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Institute For Social Research 1946-1956, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: A Program of Research on the Fundamental Problems of Organizing Human Behavior, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: A Program of Research on the Fundamental Problems of Organizing Human Behavior, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Annual Report Survey Research Center 1950, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Viewpoints and Attitudes, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: 63/64 Annual Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Annual Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Annual Report 1959-1960, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Annual Report Survey Research Center 1950, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: The Research Center for Group Dynamics, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
    By Dorwin Cartwright. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Bi-Monthly Calendar, Publication (Box 35, Folder 24)
    March-April. Item is in English.
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Plan of Representation of Employes of Midvale Steel and Ordnance Company Cambria teel Company and Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Midvale Beneficial Association By-Laws And Certificate For Membership, Publication (Box 35, Folder 25)
    March 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Copy of Agreement By and Between Milwaukee Solvay Coke Company and A. F. of L. Affiliated Unions, Publication (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Copy Of Agreement By and Between Milwaukee Solvay Coke Company and A. F. L. Affiliated Unions, Publication (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: step into a Wondeful Future, Publication (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: How Minneapolis Gas Company Studies Trends In Job Preferences Over A 15-Year Period, Publication (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Newletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 13: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 14: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 15: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 16: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 17: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 18: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
    February-March. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 20: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
    October-November. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 22: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 23: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 24: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 25: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 26: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 27: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 28: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 29: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 30: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 31: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 32: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 33: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 34: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 35: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 36: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 37: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 38: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 39: ISR Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
    Autumn. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 41: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 42: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 43: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 44: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 45: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 46: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 47: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Item 48: Newsletter, Publication (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Employee Suggestion, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: The Honeywell World, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: What Do You Suggest, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: How to read our Annual report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: welcome to Honeywell, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Honeywell, Publication (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Box: 35, folder: (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: your new job, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Your New Job, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: The Engineering And Technical Personnel Policies Of Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Company Minneapolis Operations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
    July 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Co. Application For Employment, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: The Engineering And Technical Personnel Policies Of Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Company Minneapolis Operations, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
    April 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: your new job, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 7: Honeywell, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Minneapolis Honeywell First in Controls Personnel Department 1958 Annual Report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
    January 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The office worker look at her job, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Interviewer's Manual, Publication (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Box: 36, folder: 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution And By Laws, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Minneapolis Honeywell First in Controls, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement Minneapolis-Honeywell Regular Company Brown Instruments Division and United Instrument Workers Local No. 116, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Joint Statement On "Plan For Progress", Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Prairie Gold, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your Minneapolis-Moline Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minnesota Administrative Regulations, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Minnesota Administrative Regulations Department Of Employment Security, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations of The Division Of Labor Conciliation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Summary of Minnesota State Fair Employment Practices Law, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Fair Employment Practices, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Pre-Employment Inquiry Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: 4 Years On The Job In Michigan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: State of Minnesota Fair Employment Practices Law, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: St. Paul Plant News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: St. Paul Plant News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 1951 Employees' Annual Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Mandonian, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Mandonian, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Mando, Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Rules department of civil service personnel, Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Welcome to the University of Minnesota, Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: faculty information bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: industrial relations programs, Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: industrial relations programs, Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Minnesota IRC News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: IR Teaching and Research Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Workers Education Newsletter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Workers Education Newsletter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Workers Education Newsletter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Workers Education Newsletter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Workers Education Newsletter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Mississippi State University Faculty Handbook, Publication (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A Summary of Personnel Policies and Procedures, Publication (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Missouri and Federal Laws relating to Discrimination in Employment Because of Sex, Publication (Box 36, Folder 18)
    March 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Industrial Accident Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Industrial Accident Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Industrial Accident Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Industrial Accident Report First Six Months, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Industrial Accident Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Positive Program For Employee Morale Improvement Through Communications Reports, Publication (Box 36, Folder 20)
    By G. K. Weigel. June 14. Item is in English.
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Opportunities For A Mechanical Career With The Missouri Pacific Railroad System, Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Opportunities For You In Railroading, Publication (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Mitre Matrix, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Mitre Matrix, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Mitre Matrix, Publication (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Mitre Corporation Annual Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: M & R Dietetic Laboratories, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Careers Unlimitedplan your future at, Publication (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Your Career With Mohawk Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Your Career With Mohawk Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Your Career With Mohawk Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: You And Mohawk, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Your Career With Mohawk Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Supervisory Personnel Evaluation Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Box: 36, folder: (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Report To The Stockholders Of Mohawk Airlines Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: The Air Chief, Publication (Box 36, Folder 27)